{
    "subject": "resource/Dead_Game",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Hoot_Gibson",
    "human_readable": "The movie Dead Game stars Hoot Gibson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7642756700515747,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie starring Hoot Gibson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6971819996833801,
            "question": "Who starred in the movie Dead Game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6223540306091309,
            "question": "Is Hoot Gibson an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6044808626174927,
            "question": "Can you name another movie starring Hoot Gibson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5179582238197327,
            "question": "What is Hoot Gibson known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40582290291786194,
            "question": "What was the plot of Dead Game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3261643946170807,
            "question": "Where was the movie Dead Game filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31461283564567566,
            "question": "When was the movie Dead Game released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2959255874156952,
            "question": "What genre is the movie Dead Game likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14760355651378632,
            "question": "Are there any famous directors who worked on Dead Game?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The movie Dead Game stars Hoot Gibson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4655_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the movie Dead Game likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4655_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the movie Dead Game released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4655_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the movie Dead Game filmed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4655_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4655_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4655_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4655_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4655_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4655_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4655_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4655_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4655_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4655_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4655_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention Hoot Gibson as the star of the film \"Dead Game\" (1923)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Hoot Gibson appeared in films such as \"Dead Game\" (1923). Therefore, the statement \"The movie Dead Game stars Hoot Gibson\" is correct according to the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}